Edoardo Lanari

email: edoardo.lanari.el@gmail.com website: https://edolana.github.io

Summary

Mathematician with over 4 years of experience in mathematical research. I have a strong scientific record, and I am now looking for applications of my skillset to a more applied, data-driven position in Data Science, Machine Learning or Quantitative Research.

Skills

• Higher Category Theory

• Homotopy Theory

• Python

• SQL

• (Topological) Data Analysis

• Algorithms and Data Structures

Job Experience

2020present Lecturer in Object-Oriented Programming, Prague College.

2019present Postdoctoral Researcher in Mathematics, Institute of Mathematics CAS, Prague.

2018-2019

Lecturer in Mathematics at Charles University, Prague.

2015-2018

Teaching Assistant, Macquarie University, Sydney.

Education

2020attending MITx MicroMaster Program in Statistics and Data Science.

2015-2018

 $\ensuremath{\mathsf{PHD}}$ in Mathematics, Macquarie University Faculty of Mathematics and Statistics, Sydney.

2013-2015

DOUBLE MASTER DEGREE in Mathematics, magna cum laude, University of Padova (Italy) and University of Leiden (The Netherlands).

2010-2013

BSc in Mathematics, magna cum laude, University of Trento, Italy.

For more information (list of publications, teaching material, etc...) please visit my website.